https://petfbi.org/privacy-policy/

HomeI Lost A DogChecklist for Lost DogsSearch ReportsPost ReportLost Dog: What To Do9 Steps To Finding a Lost Pet InfographicFlyer TemplateTips for Posting Lost and Found Pet FlyersWhom to ContactOther Online ResourcesLost Dog BehaviorDogs Lost Away From HomeThe “REWARD!” DebateStolen PetsI Lost A CatChecklist for Lost CatsSearch ReportsPost ReportLost Cat: What to DoTips To Lure A Cat Back Home9 Steps To Finding a Lost Pet InfographicFlyer TemplateTips for Posting Lost and Found Pet FlyersWhom to ContactOther Online ResourcesLost Cat BehaviorThe “REWARD!” DebateStolen PetsOther Lost PetsLost Birds, Rabbits, Ferrets, Reptiles, etc.Search ReportsPost ReportFlyer TemplateTips for Posting Lost and Found Pet FlyersWhom to ContactOther Online ResourcesI Found A PetChecklist for Found PetsSearch ReportsPost ReportFound Pet: What to doFlyer TemplateWhom to ContactOther Online ResourcesProtect Your PetStolen PetsTips to Protect PetsDisaster Preparedness for PetsSpay/NeuterHow to HelpDonateAnyone Can Help!Shop for CharityVolunteer ApplicationManual For Pet FBI “Special Agents”Facebook & Social Media SharePost Our FlyerBlogHappy TailsLost and Found Pet IssuesNewsWARNINGS!About Pet FBIThe Pet FBI StoryWhy Use Pet FBI?Our PartnersWho Are We?Pet FBI on Radio and TV!Nancy’s PageFinancialsHomeI Lost A Dog-Checklist for Lost Dogs-Search Reports-Post Report-Lost Dog: What To Do-9 Steps To Finding a Lost Pet Infographic-Flyer Template-Tips for Posting Lost and Found Pet Flyers-Whom to Contact-Other Online Resources-Lost Dog Behavior-Dogs Lost Away From Home-The “REWARD!” Debate-Stolen PetsI Lost A Cat-Checklist for Lost Cats-Search Reports-Post Report-Lost Cat: What to Do-Tips To Lure A Cat Back Home-9 Steps To Finding a Lost Pet Infographic-Flyer Template-Tips for Posting Lost and Found Pet Flyers-Whom to Contact-Other Online Resources-Lost Cat Behavior-The “REWARD!” Debate-Stolen PetsOther Lost Pets-Lost Birds, Rabbits, Ferrets, Reptiles, etc.-Search Reports-Post Report-Flyer Template-Tips for Posting Lost and Found Pet Flyers-Whom to Contact-Other Online ResourcesI Found A Pet-Checklist for Found Pets-Search Reports-Post Report-Found Pet: What to do-Flyer Template-Whom to Contact-Other Online ResourcesProtect Your Pet-Stolen Pets-Tips to Protect Pets-Disaster Preparedness for Pets-Spay/NeuterHow to Help-Donate-Anyone Can Help!-Shop for Charity-Volunteer Application-Manual For Pet FBI “Special Agents”-Facebook & Social Media Share-Post Our FlyerBlog-Happy Tails-Lost and Found Pet Issues-News-WARNINGS!About Pet FBI-The Pet FBI Story-Why Use Pet FBI?-Our Partners-Who Are We?-Pet FBI on Radio and TV!-Nancy’s Page-Financials
Privacy PolicyHome / Privacy PolicyPet FBI Privacy PolicyYour use of PetFBI.org is subject to Pet FBI’s Privacy Policy. Please review our Privacy Policy as set forth herein, which also governs the Site and informs users of Pet FBI’s data collection practices.Pet FBI does not sell any information you share in your report on the lost and found pet database.We have deliberately chosen to establish this web site on a basis of trust. No intermediary exists between you and the person who may have found your pet, or the person who is looking for the pet you have found. In the matter of lost pets, time – even just minutes – can make or break a successful recovery.We partner with volunteer groups that manage your listing and they may contact you to offer their assistance. None of the groups charge a fee for their service. You may also be contacted by shelters, vet clinics or other individuals that may have information about the pet you listed. Your listing will be sent via email to our members in your area. Additionally, your listing may be posted on websites and social media platforms by our partner organizations and by individuals receiving your listing.You must provide a valid email address so people can get in touch with you and so you can access your report to make changes. Your email address is your user name for access to the “Modify Report” page.While we strive to ensure the information on the Pet FBI site is accurate, the accuracy and content is the sole responsibility of the member who has posted it. Our goal is to maintain a friendly cooperative community of people who love pets and want to help others.
